Dear CEE - 298 Class:

The homework for Wednesday consists of extending the Differential
Evolution code to multiple objective problems. I am attaching a script
that gives you the Pareto rank (NmbOfFront) from a matrix of Objective
function values, ObjVals.

ObjVals is N x d, where N is the number of individuals of the population
(population size) and d denotes the number of objective function values.
This code is generic. Whatever population size or no. of objective
function value, it will work. Note that the code assumes that a value of 0
of the OFs is the best; so minimization.

Please try to solve the 2 dimensional problem discussed in the slides (the
mathematical test function), and Case Study 4.1 in the attached paper.
Figure 5 in that paper presents the results.

Please write a code that solves both multiple objective problems and
writes the output to the screen.

Kind regards,
Jasper